<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SelectionActivity</string>
    <string name="label">Click an image below to view</string>
    <string-array
        name="game_name">
        <item>Horizon Forbidden West</item>
        <item>God of War Ragnarök</item>
        <item>Black Myth: Wukong</item>
        <item>Dark Souls III</item>
        <item>Genshin Impact</item>
        <item>Ghost of Tsushima</item>
        <item>Mafia: Definitive Edition</item>
        <item>Monster Hunter: World</item>
        <item>Spider-Man</item>
        <item>Wolfenstein II</item>
        <item>The Legend of Zelda</item>
        <item>Red Dead Redemption 2</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array
        name="game_description">
        <item>Horizon Forbidden West is an action role-playing video game developed by Guerrilla Games and published by Sony Interactive Entertainment for the PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5.</item>
        <item>God of War Ragnarök is an upcoming action-adventure hack and slash video game developed by Santa Monica Studio and will be published by Sony Interactive Entertainment.</item>
        <item>Black Myth: Wukong is an upcoming action role-playing game by Chinese indie developer Game Science, based on the classical 16th-century Chinese novel Journey to the West.</item>
        <item>Dark Souls III is a 2016 action role-playing video game developed by FromSoftware and published by Bandai Namco Entertainment for PlayStation 4, Xbox One, and Microsoft Windows.</item>
        <item>Genshin Impact is an action role-playing game developed by Chinese developer miHoYo, and first published in 2020. The game features an anime-style open-world environment and an action-based battle system using elemental magic and character-switching.</item>
        <item>Ghost of Tsushima is a 2020 action-adventure game developed by Sucker Punch Productions and published by Sony Interactive Entertainment.</item>
        <item>Mafia: Definitive Edition is a 2020 action-adventure game developed by Hangar 13 and published by 2K Games. It is a remake of the 2002 video game Mafia, and the fourth main installment in the Mafia series.</item>
        <item>Monster Hunter: World is an action role-playing game developed and published by Capcom and the fifth mainline installment in the Monster Hunter series.</item>
        <item>Marvels Spider-Man is a 2018 action-adventure game developed by Insomniac Games and published by Sony Interactive Entertainment.</item>
        <item>Wolfenstein II: The New Colossus is a 2017 action-adventure first-person shooter video game developed by MachineGames and published by Bethesda Softworks.</item>
        <item>The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild is a 2017 action-adventure game developed and published by Nintendo for the Nintendo Switch and Wii U consoles.</item>
        <item>Red Dead Redemption 2 is a 2018 action-adventure game developed and published by Rockstar Games. The game is the third entry in the Red Dead series and is a prequel to the 2010 game Red Dead Redemption.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>